我不得不说  我越读有关
I gotta tell you, the more I read about the
原始重力波的发现  我就越兴奋
primordial gravity wave discovery, the more excited I get.
是啊  现在当个天体物理学家
I know. Being an astrophysicist right now
就跟当个摇滚巨星似的
is like being a rock star.
除了没歌迷送炮之外
Only without the sex.
是啊  真是一炮难求
Yeah, literally, none of it.
谢尔顿  你觉得呢
What do you think about it, Sheldon?
切
Meh.
你不是吧  这可能是
Are you kidding me? This may be
我们有生之年所能碰见最大的科研突破
the biggest scientific breakthrough of our lifetime.
而你做为个理论物理学家
How can you, as a theoretical physicist,
居然一点都不关心
not care about this?
可能我不是个精英主义者
Maybe it's because I'm not an elitist.
我更想知道的是
What I'd like to know is:
这个重力波的突破
How does this gravity wave breakthrough
能对一般人有何帮助
help the man on the street? You know?
普通路人傻逼对量子物理学的担心
Wh-Who's looking out for Joe Six-Pack
又有谁关心呢
and all his quantum physics concerns?
天啊  你在嫉妒人家
Oh, my God, you're jealous.
-我为何要嫉妒  -不知道啊
- Why would I be jealous? - Oh, I don't know.
可能宇宙的起源被别人证明了
Maybe because the origin of the universe just got proven,
希格斯力场也被别人证明了
the Higgs field just got proven
而你这20年来对弦理论的研究
and you've been working on string theory
与你刚开始的那会相比
for the last 20 years and you're no closer to proving it
一点进展都没有
than when you started.
是啊  我有太多事情要忙
Yeah, well, I've had a lot on my plate.
我们刚好活在电视界的黄金时期
We happen to live in a golden age of television.
各位  打扰一下
Excuse me, fellas.
抱歉我偷听了你们的谈话
Sorry for eavesdropping,
但其实今天在强子对撞机那里
but there actually was some big string theory news today
-有一条弦理论的大新闻呢  -真的吗
- out of the Hadron Collider. - Really?
他们发现支持额外维度的证明
Did they find evidence to support extra dimensions
-还是超对称性吗  -都不是
- or supersymmetry? - No,
但他们发现了  你什么话都信的证明
but they did find evidence that you'll believe anything.
你为何要这样
Why would you do that?
你也是个弦理论学家啊
You're a string theorist as well.
错了  我是弦理论实用家
Incorrect. I am a string pragmatist.
我跟人说我要证明一个不能被证明的理论
I say I'm gonna prove something that cannot be proved,
然后申请研究款项
I apply for grant money,
最后拿这笔钱去喝酒泡妞
and then I spend it on liquor and broads.
再会
Later.
你们觉得他说的对吗
Do you think he's right?
我把生命浪费在了一个不能被证明的理论上
Am I wasting my life on a theory that can never be proven?
或许吧  可是《权力的游戏》多好看啊
Maybe. But how great is Game of Thrones?
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
这么早就醒啦
Hey, you're up early.
我睡不着
I couldn't sleep.
我早说了别用《行尸走肉》的枕头套
I told you those Walking Dead pillowcases were a bad idea.
跟那个无关
No, that's not it.
有烦心事吗
Is something bothering you?
是啊  不过你不会懂的
Yes, but you wouldn't understand.
别这样  说来听听
Oh, come on, try me.
好吧
All right.
我把我的人生黄金时期都奉献给了弦理论
I've devoted the prime of my life to string theory
致力于探索紧化额外维度
and its quest for the compactification of extra dimensions.
而我连一点可以炫耀的成功都没有  像个傻瓜
I've got nothing to show for it, and I feel like a fool.
好  我懂了
Okay. I get it.
虽然中间的鬼话一个字没懂  但是...
I mean, not all the jibberjabber in the middle, but...
我懂那种
I know what it's like
全心全意都奉献给某个人事物
to put your heart and soul into something
却一点回报都没有的感觉
and get nothing out of it.
你是说你的演艺事业吗
You mean your acting career?
不是
No.
你与莱纳德的感情吗
Your relationship with Leonard?
也不是
No.
你重回校园的失败之路吗
Your failed attempt to go back to college?
不是
No!
我是说你与弦理论就像一段感情
I'm saying you and string theory sound like a relationship,
而我知道那种感情的滋味
and I know what it's like to be in one
也懂那种永远不能如愿的感觉
and realize it's never gonna turn out the way you want.
都说是莱纳德  你还否认
I said Leonard; you said no.
我是指跟其他男人时啦
I'm talking about other guys.
好吧
Okay.
那你都是怎么做的
Well, what do you do?
你得有壮士断腕的勇气结束感情
You have to have the courage to end the relationship.
分手止损  握手道别  甩手走人
You know? Break it off, shake hands, walk away.
我不知道我能不能做到
I don't know if I can do that.
我知道这很困难  但宝贝
I know it's hard, honey,
但人都是这样成长的
but in the end, that's how you grow.
佩妮  你有看到我好的那个吸入器吗
Penny, have you seen my good inhaler?
分手止损  握手道别  甩手走人
Break it off, shake hands, walk away.
跟两个女人纠缠得如何啊
Hey, how's dating two women going?
遇到点小麻烦
Um, kind of hit a bump.
当我老实告诉艾米丽
When I was honest and told Emily
我同时有在与另一个人约会时  她可以接受
she wasn't the only person I was seeing, it went great.
所以我也这么告诉了露西
So I tried the same thing with Lucy.
然后呢
And?
她内心五味杂陈
She had mixed feelings.
但当我说"艾米丽可以接受
But when I said, "Emily was cool with it.
艾米丽最好了  你为啥不学学艾米丽"时
Emily's the best. Why can't you be more like Emily?"...
那五味就只剩一味了
...those feelings became less mixed.
女人啊  谁知道她们不爽的点在哪
Women. Who knows what'll set 'em off?
可至少我现在能全心对一个女孩投入了
At least now I can focus all my energies on just one girl.
我希望我能尽快见到她
I hope I get to meet her as soon as possible.
干嘛这么着急  她又不会跑
Why the rush? She isn't going anywhere.
她会的  但我喜欢你的乐观
She is. But I like that attitude.
各位  有人对我弦理论的旧书感兴趣吗
Gentlemen, is anybody interested in my old string theory books?
你真的要这么做吗
You're really going to do this?
是的  佩妮指出
I am. Yeah, Penny pointed out that
我现在基本上就是在经历一段分手
what I'm going through is essentially a breakup.
而且根据《时尚》杂志中
And according to Cosmopolitan magazine,
一篇教导如何有效挥别旧爱的文章
one of the most effective techniques for moving on
分手就得丢掉会回忆起感情的一切物件
is to get rid of all reminders of the relationship.
-你还读起《时尚》杂志啦  -是啊
- You're reading Cosmo? - Yes.
而且我还发现  基本上
As it turns out, there's an article
每期都有教导如何挥别旧爱的文章
on how to get over a breakup in literally every issue.
反正
Anyway,
它还建议要把这些东西烧掉
it suggests that I set these on fire,
但烧书的味道
but the smell of burning books
会让我想起教会去德州东部野餐时的回忆
reminds me of church picnics in East Texas.
这是什么
What's this?
我随手画的超椭圆黎曼曲面而已
That's just a doodle of a hyperelliptic Riemann surface.
这不是你当年博士后的基础吗
Oh, yeah. Wasn't that the basis of your postdoc fellowship?
是啊
It was.
当年我还觉得这很高大上
This seemed so elegant at the time,
但我现在意识到我当年只是个被
but... now I realize I was just a simple country boy
大城市那变量都对的理论
seduced by a big city theory
所迷惑的单纯农村小伙
with variables in all the right places.
-你会没事的  -我知道
- It's going to be okay. - I know.
尽管很困难  我还是得挥别过去了
As hard as this is, I have to move on.
我不能再一直假定着多维度实体
I can't keep postulating multidimensional entities
却什么结果也得不到
and get nothing in return.
我也是有需求的人
I have needs, too.
你现在还跟艾米丽在一起吗
So, you and Emily still together?
我问过伯纳黛特了  她明天有空
I spoke to Bernadette. She's free tomorrow night.
好啊  行
Oh, okay, great.
但如果我们真的要四人约会
But if we're really gonna do a double date,
我们得先定下一些跟艾米丽有关的规矩
then we have to go over some ground rules about Emily.
比如最终发现她是个橡胶充气娃娃时
Like when it turns out she's made of rubber,
我啥都不许说吗
I don't say anything?
她很真实好吗
She's very real.
充气娃娃盒子上都这么写啊
Oh, that's what it says on the box.
就写在"可用洗碗机清洗"的字样旁
Right next to "Dishwasher safe."
你看
See?
我担心的就是
This is exactly the kind of thing
你在她面前说这类的话
I'm worried about you saying in front of her.
-我保证我绝对会很乖  -最好是这样
- I promise I'll be on my best behavior. - You better be.
不许开我跟我的狗很亲密的玩笑
No jokes about how close I am with my dog.
也不许说我跟我狗有多亲密的实话
Or the truth about how close I am with my dog.
我保证
You got it.
不许开我学过一年芭蕾舞的玩笑
No jokes about the year I took ballet.
你学过芭蕾舞吗
You took ballet?
天啊  你从来都不好好聆听
God, you never listen.
你确定你要这样吗
Are you sure you want to do this?
杂志中一篇文章建议
The magazine articles suggest that one of the ways
挥别旧情的方法就是新造型
to get over a breakup is a new look.
那你的旧造型呢
What about your old look,
精心打扮过的腹语术玩偶造型
well-groomed ventriloquist doll?
-"天啊  的确是很像"  -别闹了
- "Oh, my God, I do look like that." - Stop it!
所以你想我怎么剪
So, how do you want me to cut it?
比尔·盖兹加尼古拉·特斯拉的发型
How about Bill Gates meets Nikola Tesla?
就是前面商人头  后面科学家头
So, business in the front, science in the back.
或者我就不剪了
Or I don't cut it
就搞点造型就行了
and maybe just style it a little.
你说了算
Oh, I'm in your hands.
你弄得好我就告诉你  《时尚》教你如何轻松度过
Do a good job and I'll tell you Cosmo's ten dynamite tips
经前症候群的10大绝招
to enjoy your PMS.
你能让他保持安静吗
Can you keep him quiet?
比如拿钥匙在他眼前晃
Maybe jangle some keys in front of him?
这招不好用了
That doesn't work anymore.
他只会觉得我是要带他去看医生
He just thinks I'm taking him to the doctor.
所以你现在不搞弦理论了
So, now that you're no longer invested in string theory,
你打算研究哪方面
what are you gonna pursue?
有很多超有意思的领域啊
Oh, there are so many exciting areas:
黑洞  暗物质
black holes, dark matter...
莱纳德那天还在跟我说暗物质呢
Oh, Leonard was telling me about dark matter,
但我真的不太理解
but I didn't really understand it.
不用难过  他自己也不懂
Don't feel bad. Neither does he.
好了
Okay...
你觉得如何
what do you think?
你看没看过特斯拉的照片啊
Have you ever even seen a picture of Tesla?
尼古拉·特斯拉  伟大的发明家  物理学家
发型是微卷的中分头
其实很好看呢  谢尔顿
It actually looks good, Sheldon.
-是吧  -是啊
- Doesn't it? - Yeah.
我是可以想象自己在一个科学男子团体里
I suppose I could see myself in a scientific boy band.
由于美貌与智慧并存  所以在男团里一个顶俩
Of course, I'd be the dreamy one and the smart one.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
你干了啥好事
What did you do?
我帮他弄了新造型  很好看吧
I gave him a new look. It's cute, huh?
是啊  很好看  这就是问题
Yeah, it's cute. That's the problem.
我可不想他走在路上被饥渴的女人们
I don't need other girls to see him walking around
扑上来按倒
like sex on a stick.
她说的对  我太性感了
She's right. I'm too hot.
我迫不及待想见艾米丽
I'm excited to meet Emily.
我也是  只希望他别搞砸这段情
Me, too. I just hope he doesn't blow it.
你为什么这么说
Why would you say that?
因为他是拉杰啊  这是他的专长
Because he's Raj-- that's his thing.
贝克汉姆很会踢球  破坏王很会砸
Beckham can bend it, Ralph can wreck it,
电影《Bend it like Beckham》我爱贝克汉姆
与《Wreck it Ralph》无敌破坏王
拉杰很会搞砸
Raj can blow it.
我也不想发生那种事
Look, I don't want it to happen,
但他有很大的几率会搞...
but odds are he's gonna find a way to...
靠  我认识那女的
Oh, crap, I know that girl.
怎么个认识
How?
很不好  非常不好的认识
In a bad way, very bad.
你们好啊
Hey, guys.
无论你今晚听到了什么  只要记得我很爱你
Whatever you hear tonight, just remember I love you.
你们来啦
Hey!
艾米丽  他们是我的好朋友
Emily, these are my good friends,
霍华德与伯纳黛特
Howard and Bernadette.
-两位  她叫艾米丽  -幸会
- Guys, this is Emily. - Nice to meet you.
你好
Hi.
我们见过吗
Have we met before?
没有吧
Uh... no.
我  我觉得  没有吧
I-I don't... I don't... think so.
你确定吗  你好眼熟啊
You sure? You look familiar.
你肯定看错了
Well, you sure don't.
我认识你  我也认识你  而你...
You I know, you I know, you?
绝对是初次见面啊
Total stranger.
就算你有好吃的糖果  我也不会跟你去看金鱼
Even if you had yummy candy, I would not get in your van.
你是不是有参加格林街上的自行车健身班
Did you go to that spin class on Green Street?
就是这样没错
That must be it.
你什么时候参加过自行车健身班
Since when do you go to spin class?
看看到底谁才不听别人说话
Wow. Now who doesn't listen?
谢尔顿  你的饭都快凉了
Sheldon, your food's getting cold.
你在干什么呢
What are you doing?
我想从课本里找出新的研究方向
Oh, looking through my textbooks for a new field of inquiry.
家里怎么会有本地质学的书
Why do we have a Geology book?
莱纳德
Leonard,
我回去德州时  你在家偷偷办了个儿童派对吗
did you throw a children's party while I was in Texas?
等等  地理学怎么惹到你了
Wait. What's wrong with geology?
让我用你能听懂的方式解释吧  佩妮
Let me put this in a way you'll understand, Penny.
记得你跟我解释过
You remember how you explained to me
卡戴珊一家根本算不上真正的明星吗
that the Kardashians aren't real celebrities?
地理学就是科学界的卡戴珊一家
Well, Geology is the Kardashians of science.
你考虑过研究标准模型物理学吗
Have you considered studying standard model physics?
你想让我放弃弦理论
You want me to give up string theory
去做更落后的项目吗
for something that's less advanced?
那你为什么不甩掉佩妮
You know, why don't you break up with Penny
去找个棕熊恋爱呢
and start dating a brown bear?
好像你泡得到棕熊似的
Like you could get a brown bear.
人家有份正经工作
Hey, I've got a good job.
有钱买三文鱼给熊吃  搞不好会成功呢
I could buy salmon. You don't know.
或许你可以开始尝试一下
Maybe you could make your new field of study
核矩阵元素的计算工作
the calculation of nuclear matrix elements.
得了吧
Oh, please.
如果我想赶时髦  还不如去搞个骚女纹身呢
If I wanted to take up a fad, I'd get a tramp stamp.
那环圈量子重力学呢
What about loop quantum gravity?
公爵夫人  瞧瞧我
Oh, Duchess, look at me.
我的量子重力学真是好糊涂[圈]啊
My quantum gravity's positively loopy.
公爵夫人是哪位啊
Who's the Duchess?
他脑子里众多幻想人物之一
One of the people that lives in his head.
如果他和我分手后  也这么心神错乱就好了
I hope he's this distraught if he ever breaks up with me.
如果真是  我会让我家熊熊替他介绍对象的
Well, if he does, I'll see if my bear has a friend.
谢尔顿  你可以试试
Sheldon, have you ever considered
不要急着开始新的研究呀
not rushing into something new?
你为什么不放松一点
I mean, why don't you take your time,
享受享受自由的时间呢
enjoy your freedom?
也许新的课题会主动出现在你面前
Maybe something new to study will find you.
这个建议其实还真不错
That's actually not bad advice.
你知道  我当初也不是主动研究弦理论的
You know, I didn't seek out string theory.
有一天它就突然对我当头棒喝
It just hit me over the head one day.
怎么发生的
How does that happen?
一个校园恶霸在图书馆追着我跑
A bully chased me through the school library
用他手边最重的书打了我的头
and hit me over the head with the biggest book he could find.
我们来为你的自由干杯吧
Okay, how about we toast your newfound freedom?
通常我是不沾酒的
Ah, normally I refrain from alcohol,
但我的大脑皮层已经在无聊地玩手指了
but since my cerebral cortex is twiddling its proverbial thumbs,
不如就让它沉浸在
why not soak it in grape juice
霉菌发酵过的葡萄汁里吧
that's been predigested by a fungus?
怪不得其他孩子要用书砸你呢
And you wonder why other children beat you with books.
干杯
Cheers!
艾米丽  你是做什么工作的
Emily, what do you do?
我是亨廷顿医院的皮肤科医师
I'm a dermatology resident at Huntington Hospital.
你们都懂其中的意思了吧
Mmm, and you know what that means.
有人的皮肤马上就要吹弹可破了
Someone's skin's about to be softer than ever.
这可折磨死我了
This is making me crazy.
我知道我肯定在哪里见过你
I know I know you from somewhere.
霍华德曾经做过宇航员
Oh, uh, Howard was an astronaut.
也许你就是这么认识他的
Maybe that's where you saw him.
太厉害了
That's amazing.
那是什么样的感觉
What was that like?
是我人生中最难忘的体验
It was the most incredible experience of my life.
在太空站里  人会...
Up there in the space station, you're...
我的妈呀  我想起来了
Oh, my God, I remember.
能让我把宇航员的故事说完吗
Can I finish my astronaut story?
这事发生在四年前
It was four years ago.
-求求你别说出来  -别人介绍我们相亲
- Please don't say it. - We were set up on a blind date.
-别说下去了  拜托  -你来了我的公寓
- Please don't say it. - You came to my apartment.
你还是说出来了
You're saying it.
到底发生了什么
Well, wh-what happened?
-是啊  发生了什么事  -好吧  我来说吧
- Yeah, what happened? - Okay, I'll say it.
我去她家接她
I was on the way to pick her up.
路上我的肠胃开始不舒服了
My stomach felt a little funny.
所以到她家时  我借用了她的厕所
When I got there, I asked if I could use her bathroom.
求你别说了
Please don't say it.
20分钟过去了  在用完一卷卫生纸后
One roll of toilet paper and 20 minutes later,
我实在是太羞愧难当
I was so humiliated,
于是我从窗口逃走了  再也没敢去见她
I snuck out the window and never saw her again.
你知道还有什么也跟着你消失了吗
You know what else I never saw again--
我付给房东的清洁押金
my security deposit.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我试着疏通马桶  可找不到马桶塞子
I tried to unclog it, but you didn't have a plunger,
水也流得到处都是
and water was spilling out everywhere.
对  流的只是"水"而已
Right, just water.
这些年我都一直为这事而羞愧
Look, I have felt terrible about this for years,
我也很庆幸今天有这个机会
and I'm glad I have the opportunity
当面向你表达我的歉意
to tell you just how sorry I am.
没关系
It's fine.
我的朋友们都好爱这个故事
All my friends love this story.
他们叫你"卡屎拉"
They call you Clogzilla.
你懂吗
Get it?
因为你是一只卡住了她家马桶的
Because you clogged up her bathroom
怪兽哥斯拉
like a radioactive monster!
我听懂了
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
华仔
Howie.
你拉的屎也没有跟棉花糖一样美啊
Well, hey, it's not like cotton candy comes out of you.
快点  我们回家睡觉了
Come on, let's get you to bed.
你可喝了不少呢
You've had a lot to drink.
-我不比佩妮喝得多  -所以说你喝了不少啊
- No more than Penny. - That's what I'm saying.
等...等等  等一下
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
空房间
Empty room.
如果有人说"请进"  会把我吓死
If somebody says "Come in," I'm gonna freak out.
艾米丽
So, Emily,
你为什么会选择专攻皮肤学呢
why did you decide to specialize in dermatology?
我喜欢用刀割人
I like cutting people with knives,
而其它割人的工作都是违法的
and all the other jobs where you get to do that are illegal.
你是开玩笑的吧
You're kidding, right?
她让人怕怕  不过是可爱的怕怕
She's scary, but it's a cute scary.
我可以再补充一点吗
Can I say just one more thing?
我那天是食物中毒了
I had some kind of food poisoning that day.
当然现在回想起来  加油站寿司
Sure, in retrospect, gas station sushi--
不是什么明智的选择
maybe not the best choice.
当然爬出你家窗户逃走也不对
Nor was climbing out your window and running away.
但我想  大家都能理解那情形有多丢人
But I think we can all understand how humiliating that was,
如果咱们能既往不咎  我会非常感激的
and I'd really appreciate it if we could move on.
华仔  已经既往不咎一段时间了
Howie, we moved on a long time ago.
-我只是说...-已经既往不咎了
- I'm just saying... - We moved on.
好吧  行
Okay. Fine.
你的汤怎么样
How's your soup?
还行
Ah, it's all right.
他们可以把碗[马桶]再装得满一点
They could've filled the bowl a little more.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
我需要呼吸下新鲜空气
I need some fresh air.
我当时也是
Been there.
我去
Oh, no.
我做了什么
What have I done?
感觉怎样
How you feeling?
不太好
Not so good.
不向我介绍一下你的这位朋友吗
Are you gonna introduce me to your friend?
这不是我的朋友
It's not my friend.
什么事也没有发生
Nothing happened.
是吗  你昨晚读它的声音可是相当"大"哦
I don't know. I heard you reading pretty loud last night.
我的老天啊
Oh, dear Lord.
艾米呢
Where's Amy?
她把你扶上床休息后就回家了
After she put you to bed, she went home.
我应该打电话给她道歉
I should call her and apologize.
-不好  -怎么了
- Oh, no. - What?
看来我昨晚打了电话给史蒂芬·霍金
Apparently, I called Stephen Hawking last night.
第一条新留言
First new message.
霍哥
Hawkman!
我是你铁哥们儿谢肠镜啊
It's your old buddy Sheldonoscopy!
你为什么不接电话呢
How come you didn't pick up the phone?!
你的手动不了  我错了
Oh, right. My bad.
你出奇的安静啊  还好吗
You're awful quiet. Everything okay?
不太好
Not really.
我昨晚丢人丢大了
I had a bit of an embarrassing evening.
我也是  发生了什么事
Ugh. Me, too. What happened?
我喝了酒
I drank alcohol
给史蒂芬·霍金留了一通很不妙的留言
and may have left an unfortunate voice mail for Stephen Hawking.
我觉得不用担心
I wouldn't worry about it.
他这人幽默感挺强的
He's got a pretty good sense of humor.
希望如此
Oh, I hope so.
你昨晚发生了什么事
What happened to you last night?
原来
Oh, well, turns out
我以前见过拉杰的女友
I'd already met the girl Raj is seeing
我当时在她家厕所留过号码
when I did a number on her bathroom.
而那号码是"大号"
And that number was two.
我一直很喜欢尼沙布尔的阿塔尔[诗人]
Well, you know, I've always been a fan
写的一个故事
of a story told by Attar of Nishapur,
说的是一个国王
about a king
召集一群智者  制作一枚戒指
who assembled a group of wise men to create a ring
让他在悲伤时能高兴起来
that would make him happy when he was sad.
这枚戒指上
And that ring
刻了一句话  "一切都会随风而逝"
was inscribed with the phrase, "This too shall pass."
-库珀  -老天
- Hey, Cooper! - Oh, my God.
我听说你昨晚给霍金打了醉酒电话
I heard you drunk-dialed Stephen Hawking last night?
牛逼啊
Classic!
快走开  巴里
Get out of here, Barry.
你说了算
Whatever you say...
卡屎拉
Clogzilla.
卡屎拉  挺好笑的
Clogzilla. That's pretty funny.
我不觉得有风能刮走"这坨屎"
I don't think that's gonna pass.
下一条留言
Next message.
又是我
It's me again!
我放弃弦理论了
I gave up string theory.
你也应该放弃黑洞
You should give up black holes,
咱俩搭档绝对是罪案克星
and we can totally solve crimes together!
下一条留言
Next message.
你知道什么超棒吗
Do you know what's great?!
地质学
Geology.
看这个晶洞
Look at this geode!
这个词读起来真有意思
That's fun to say!
进  洞  井  洞
Gee... ode! Gee... ode!
下一条留言
Next message.
精  洞
Gee... ode!
茎  洞
小弟现在会和女生打啵啵了
I kiss girls now.
下一条留言
Next message.
猜猜我是谁
Hey, guess who I am!
哔哔嘟嘟
Beep bop boop bop!
我是你  懂了吗
I'm you! Get it?!
下一条留言
Next message.
你生我的气了吗
Are you mad at me?
不好  你生人家的气了
Oh, no, you're mad at me.
真是对不起
I'm so sorry!
哔哔嘟嘟
Beep bop boop bop.
下一条留言
Next message.
硫硼尖晶石  牛棚鸡鸡石
Thiospinel sulfide. Thiospinel sulfide.
这个念起来比"茎洞"更好玩
That's even more fun than "gee... ode."
你看了《乐高大电影》吗
Hey, did you see The Lego Movie?
傻逼
What a jackass.